{
    "id": "8ddf3bba63c846cca32e58188d59faa5",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She ………………. in",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "graduated",
                "has graduated",
                "was graduating"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4329ee23ac0449fa8593689bb593e7aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. with your performance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am impressed",
                "impressed",
                "am impressing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4e9c3d0397ac432fa638e76924c6a2d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………….. the door shut and rushed out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was slamming",
                "slammed",
                "has slammed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3cb629dfd49d408c8fe4bd3d6dcacc51"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. my leg, so I can’t walk now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have hurt",
                "hurt",
                "am hurting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "783e477a7993488fab00bff65f653b88"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………. everyone with his temper tantrums.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "annoyed",
                "annoying",
                "was annoyed",
                "was annoying"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c98af21103be4f40a8b491136cc9b19e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………. the charge.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "deny",
                "am denying",
                "was denying"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8c0805436c4040bf836ffb1e11306d81"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………. me a liar.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "called",
                "has called",
                "was calling"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "68ee0b9fc54f408081b94ab0d2abdb4a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I looked up but I …………………. anything.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "didn't see",
                "doesn't see",
                "haven't seen"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7fac7c4d8ea04fddb5d94cdc196e4885"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………….. to be an architect.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wants",
                "want",
                "is wanting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9a51d31346b54b41b7be1ec5493e51b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The plants ……………….. for want of water.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "died",
                "dead",
                "are died"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "079de49ab4a34772ae81b7e80105cdd0"
        }
    ]
}